

Contact

gusfonte99@gmail.com

+351960083813

Github

in LinkedIn

Aveiro, Portugal

Skills

Tech skills

React

Mongoose

Node.js

HTML

Express.js

CSS

MongoDB

Tailwind

JavaScript

Other

Github

Axios

Git

Postman

Agile

REST API

Soft Skills

Communication

Quick learner

Adaptability

· Customer service

Problem solving

Teamwork

Attention to detail

Organization

Language

Native **English** Portuguese Native French Professional Spanish Elementary

Gustavo Fonte

MERN Full Stack Developer

A Full Stack Web Developer with a retail background and a passion for IT. Having spent 2 years in the retail industry, I honed in my costumer service and interpersonal skills. I recently made the exciting leap to follow my passion for IT and recently finished a Full Stack Development bootcamp.

Projects

Aniki 12/2023

Anime forum

Final project developed at Ironhack with Zohra Boukhatem.

 Tech used: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, HTML, **Tailwind CSS**

Date Flow 11/2023

Collaborative date planner app

Worked alongside Hugo Manachem, as part of Module 2 of the Ironhack Web Dev bootcamp. The app is inspired by Trello and Notion.

· Tech used: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, REST API, HTML, **Tailwind CSS**

Web Dev Survivors

11/2023

2D survivor Bullet Hell game

First project developed at Ironhack Web development Bootcamp, meant to showcase the acquired skills during the first 2 weeks.

· Tech used: JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Education

Full Stack Web Development bootcamp

10/2023 - 12/2023

Ironhack

- Learned to work with a variety of web development tools and technologies.
- JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTML, CSS and Tailwind.
- Engaged in **project work**, individually and in teams.

English, Proficiency (C2)

07/2018 - 03/2020

International House Aveiro

Highschool diploma (Sciences)

09/2018 - 06/2019

Escola Secundária José Estevão

Work Experience

Salesman

02/2023 - 05/2023 Águeda, Portugal | On-site

Worten

09/2022 - 01/2023

Salesman **Staples Portugal**

Aveiro, Portugal | On-site

Customer Service Agent

Fnac

02/2022 - 06/2022 Aveiro, Portugal | On-site